Here you are, Master.
Thanks, Icarus.
I am the weapon Master despises.
I don't know if I should keep that information from him.
I wonder what Master is thinking right now.
Hmm. I wish I could find some way into the girl's bed.
I wish I could find some way into the girl's bed.
止められないよ 天使が鳴らしてる
大好きの合図だよね
Can you hear my heart?
どうしたって言うの?
聞いた事がない 誰のベリーが鳴る
それでもまた 君は何にも知らないけれど
The 15th century was the dawn of the age of exploration.
Joan of Arc followed a mysterious voice that spoke to her only in her dream.
She dressed as a man and rose to lead the French army to many victories.
It's been a long time since then, and again a youth listens to a dream.
He's about to change the world.
He will dress up in women's clothing, and he will seek out the new world.
Sugata!
Looking pretty hot.
Oh, Mikako, cut it out.
Huh, a bath together.
Tomiki said he wanted us all to go.
Of course, I tried arguing, but he wouldn't hear it.
Come on, ladies.
Sometimes an open-air bath can be the perfect thing to relax your senses.
Given this is your idea, are we sure this isn't a case of the smaller head controlling the larger one?
No, not at all.
Personal hygiene is very important at our age.
Yeah, I guess they'd drag him through the streets and beat him senseless.
Not that I wouldn't love every second of it.
Here we go.
I'll use one of Icarus's cards, and these hotties will be mine for the taking.
Okay, Icarus, why don't you hand over all of the cards you have on you?
All right.
Sorry about that, Tomo, but I know exactly what's on your devious little mind.
Figured I'd cut you off at the pass.
No!
We are going to take that bath later, but it'll be just us girls.
Thank you very much.
Ciao, buddy.
Tomo-ki, maybe a little foresight on this one would have benefited you some.
I personally don't think anything's ever going to benefit him.
They'll always be tripped up by his...
I only got one chance left.
Not interested.
But the girls are going to be bathing!
Not a stitch of clothing on any of them!
Bathing!
Don't you get it?
This is the new world.
What did you say?
What did you just say?
Think about it.
Boys can only enter the women's bath until they're what, like 10 years old?
And then we've got no chance to do it ever again.
Not for the rest of our lives.
We're cut off from that world.
And what a wondrous world it must be.
The women's bath.
So, is it not possible the new world you've been searching for is there behind those forbidden walls?
Where the heck did you get that card?
When I spoke to her earlier, I took one of these to examine for myself.
A transmogrifier.
It might not operate that stably, but it can transform you into something else nevertheless.
Use it to become a girl.
However, you can't just dive straight into the bath when you do.
To avoid suspicions, you have to completely transform into one of them first.
Only then can you seek out the new world.
Understand?
Sir! Yes, sir!
This will be a very difficult mission.
One from which you might not return.
A risk I'm more than willing to take.
I'm back!
Hi there, I'm Tomoko.
So basically, you used one of our cards so you could turn yourself into a girl?
Pretty cool, huh?
I thought it might be fun to live life as a girl for a little while.
Everything appears normal on her for the time being.
I'm a girl now, so there's a few hundred things I want to try, if you know what I mean.
Come on, let's get out of here.
I guess I'm used to seeing panties.
But now I get to wear them, so I look forward to approaching them from an entirely different way.
They put pads in the bras?
I didn't know that.
What else are they hiding from us?
Wait a sec.
Hey, Nymph, why don't you pick out a cute bra, too?
So, Hara recommends you wear something like this.
What do you think?
No way!
What is that crazy bug girl even thinking?
Why would I wear something so impractical?
It's not armored and it has no stealth properties whatsoever.
But who cares?
Don't you think it looks cuter than cube?
Check this one out.
It's adorable, huh?
Explain this concept of cute.
Great, another complicated question.
How do I get this to make sense to her?
Hmm, instead of explaining what cute is, how about I show you?
See, this is cute.
What do you think of the frilliness or how sheer the midsection is?
Well?
Yes, Master, it's very cute.
I agree.
So, Tomuki, seeing things that are cute makes you happy?
Well, I don't know if happy is the right word, but it's definitely visually pleasing.
Gotcha!
What about this?
Am I cute now?
Yeah.
Off to a good start, then!
I think I'll buy this one and see what else I can find.
Now that I'm a chick, I'm going to become the most popular chick in the entire freaking school.
Oh, wow, I'm sorry.
Geez, are you okay?
I'm fine.
You perv.
Whoa, now that girl's a hottie.
What was that all about?
A transfer student has to make an entrance, and trust me, having the heroine show up like
this will be sweet.
You really make no sense sometimes.
Icarus, Nymph, how are you two doing?
Where's Tomuki?
He said he had a cold, so he's staying home.
No way.
Tomuki caught a cold?
I've known him since forever, and he almost never gets sick.
I hope he'll be okay.
Maybe I should go visit him when school lets out this afternoon.
He'll be fine.
It's minor, but he's still very contagious.
So don't go check up on him.
Right, Alpha?
You say so.
And you are?
Nice to meet you.
My name's Tomoko.
I just transferred here.
Hope we get along like old friends.
Okay.
Sure, why not?
Sounds like a plan.
Perfect.
Zohara doesn't have a clue what's going on.
My plan is going brilliantly.
My hobby's making snacks and finger foods.
Today I made cookies.
Go on, take some.
It's my best batch yet.
I'll take one.
Yeah, a cookie sounds great.
You suck.
I'm sorry.
I'm such a titz.
I must have used salt instead of sugar.
Gosh, I hope you guys don't hate me.
No way, you're too cute.
I just transferred here like this morning,
so I really didn't have anything else to wear for home egg.
Hope you don't mind, meow.
How cute.
That's what Tomoki's talking about when he says something's cute?
I believe that is just what he perceives the perfect woman acts like.
So to be cute, we have to say meow?
Yeah.
Tomoko, why won't you wake up?
Why?
This is madness and I never want to...
I got a present for you, Tomoko.
Give me a big smile.
I don't know who I should give my attention to.
Seems Tomoko's the flavor of the week.
Something weird about her, though.
Maybe it's the way she's put together.
She reminds me of one of those anime chicks.
I guess the guys really dig that.
I mean, why the hell else would they be fawning all over her?
Watching this is enlightening.
Mm-hmm.
The time for Jim has finally arrived.
Stay calm, Tomoki.
I'll boldly go into the great unknown.
I live my life right now.
Hey, Tomoko, you know the locker next to mine is free if you'd like to use it.
Come on, check it out.
Sure.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm such a klutz sometimes.
Tomoko, you can be ridiculously cute.
If Tomoki saw you, he'd fall in love with you right on the spot.
Who?
Oh, yeah, Tomoki.
He's this guy I know.
We've been friends since we were kids.
He's in the same class as us, but you won't see him today.
He's out sick.
Basically, he's a perv and a bit of a freak,
and all he thinks about is panties.
It might sound harmless, and he might call himself a peace and quiet loving guy,
but actually, he's quite a little predator.
I would keep my eye out for him if I were you.
Holy crap, that was harsh.
So, if you're ever in trouble, he's the first person to be at your side,
and deep down, he really is a caring person.
Maybe I'm being too hard on him.
Huh?
Never mind, I was just rambling.
You pass.
I've been watching your actions today, and all of them exceed my expectations.
The way you walk, the way you move, your voice,
everything is within normal girl parameters.
Even your clumsiness has grabbed the hearts of some of the geeks out there.
All seems to be moving smoothly.
Score!
Seems I was right to go in with you on this adventure.
Even Mikiko's intuition isn't flaring up.
Tomoki, the time is at hand.
Come on!
Why don't you call me Tomoko, big boy?
A public bath?
Icarus wanted to go with everyone, said it was part of the human experience.
Yeah, so who the hell are you again?
My name's Tomoko.
I just, uh, I just transferred here this week.
When I was at my last school, I really looked up to my student council president.
I mean, seriously, she was the best.
I always wanted to get to know her better than I did.
I figure with you, I kind of get that chance at the start.
Please let me go to the bath with you guys.
I just want to be part of the group.
Is that okay?
Sure, that all sounds fine to me.
Yes!
Lucky for us, Tomoki's homesick.
We can have a nice time and not worry about him spying on us.
That's a relief.
Why don't we get a move on then?
I want to spend as much time there as I can.
Great work, Tomoki.
Now, onward to the new world.
It's been forever since I've been to a bathhouse.
Kick-ass, dude.
You look just like a real chick.
Now you just gotta work it.
It looks like you understand everything now, Tomoki.
By blending in here, you'll be just like any other girl.
I can't believe it.
This really is the new world.
Master, your heart rate is becoming erratic.
I recommend you calming down.
So this is where you ran off to?
I have to monitor Master's metamorphosis or there could be trouble.
Sounds like you're having a hell of a time with it.
Come on, Alpha.
Don't you think this is kind of dumb?
It's what Master ordered.
An order?
Huh.
If my orders were as easy as yours are, I'd be done with my mission.
Wow.
You're pretty lucky.
I bet you don't ever have to worry.
That's not true.
I remember something you said one time.
You told me I would not be able to fool Master forever.
If Master knew the truth about me, he would hate me.
And then I would never get to see him again.
But I know that lying to him is wrong.
I do not know if I can keep hiding this from him day after day.
Tomoki will be fine.
Bugs are all stupid.
He'll never notice.
I'll bury his head in the sand like they all do.
Hi there, Prez.
So, uh, you want me to give your back a good scrub while you're sitting there?
Why not?
I'll take you up on that offer.
Yes!
You've waited so long, dear hands of mine.
And you, my fiendish urges, your patience will be rewarded.
Once more into the abyss.
Geronimo!
Yes, my hand slipped.
So sorry about that, Prez.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
What's the matter?
Something up?
The metamorphosis of Master's body is altered in one area.
Master, we have a problem.
If your excitement continues at this level, it's possible an unknown metamorphosis will occur
as a result.
Master, are you there?
I can wash you, too!
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Let loose!
There's nothing to worry about.
I mean, we are all ladies here.
Master, do you require assistance?
Master, can you hear me?
We're all girls here?
Yes!
Hi, girls, dear!
Looks like the poor kid's completely lost himself.
What the hell's going on with Tomoko?
The boss turned into a battlefield.
I'm not saying that's a bad thing, mind you.
It is horribly interesting to watch.
You must calm down, Master.
If you do not, the quantum transformation device will...
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
What on earth?
Someone want to tell me what a faucet is doing stuck here?
Total meltdown.
I think I'll take my leave now.
Zora, you dropped your bath down.
Here, let me pick it up for you, if that's cool.
I don't care if you see me naked right now.
I don't care if the image stays with you forever.
All I care about is my insatiable desire to kill you!
It's a sign of wisdom, Tomoki, to know when to pull out.
That's right. Keep scrubbing till it's all good and clean.
Yes, ma'am, I will.
Oh, we can finally bathe in peace.
Yep, shouldn't be anyone else here but us right now.
It's really nice.
Yeah, I could get used to this.
With Icarus still having those wings sticking out and Nymph being worried about her choker,
it took guts coming in here.
I mean it. You have more courage than most girls our age.
Geez, I'm sorry.
I didn't even notice those things might have made you two uncomfortable.
I've just gotten used to the idea of you two as normal girls.
I forget that you're actually angeloids.
Guess I should get out of my own head a bit and think about you sometimes.
But it makes me happy.
I don't want you to change.
I want you to see me just as another normal girl.
Although what I really want is to be even more human for Master.
You're fine the way you are.
Don't change a thing.
And you can't go around lying like that time at the park, okay?
I know you better than you might think and you're bigger than that.
So no more lying.
So it is a bad thing to lie.
Yeah, it's bad. Promise me you won't do it.
There. It's a promise.
Liar, liar, pants on fire, hanging from a telephone wire.
I have to tell Master the truth now.
I made a promise.
Oh, hey. Glad you were finally able to take a bath.
The old lady in charge of the bathhouse made me scrub down the whole thing until it was freaking spotless.
Master, I have something important to tell you.
There is something I've been hiding from you for a long time now, but I'm afraid of what might happen if I tell you.
I'm afraid you might hate me.
Good job, Icarus.
Seriously, you're becoming more human every day.
You don't even realize it, do you?
Human beings always have one or two little things they hide from each other.
It's normal.
Master.
When you're ready to talk about it, let me know. We're family now.
What'd I say? I knew Tomuki would be just fine.
I wish I had a nice master.
Sugata, do you have any idea what the Angeloids actually are?
Not like I've got an answer, but when I was a kid, I thought it would be cool to have a robot maid who'd do whatever I wanted.
Really, though, in the end, I don't want Icarus to suffer for me. Not in any way.
The only thing I know for sure is that far above us in the sky, there is a new world.
Icarus and Nymph are both trapped by the rules that govern them.
I don't know the specifics.
I wonder who created the Angeloids.
I mean, somebody had to, right?
I want to punch them.
Oh
He went into a man alone
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on, come on
At the rate she's going now, she might just run away
Are you okay with that?
I'm not concerned
As long as I keep hold of this chain, she cannot escape
Besides, I've already decided to scrap her
My goodness, aren't you awful?
I can't wait
It's been a while since I've been this excited about anything
Next time, Chains of No Escape